wheresbest.co.uk 2018-12-14

# UK directory of pubs, restaurants, hotels, youth hostels and other places of interest. - Wheresbest.co.uk

This site uses cookies. By continuing to browse the site you are agreeing to our use of cookies.

We collect and use information from our customers in the following ways.

Personal information provided by you as part of your registration process is used by us to service and fulfil your account.

Any information provided by you in connection with any transaction regarding your credit or debit card numbers, expiry date and billing or delivery address will be used by us to process the transaction. These details will be stored on a secure server and may be used by us to facilitate and personalise future transactions with you.

We may use the email address provided by you to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service.

If you do not wish to receive this information, please e-mail us.

Wheresbest.co.uk uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences -- however, you must enable cookies from Wheresbest.co.uk in order to use a small number of functions of the site. You can find out more about the use of cookies on this website by reading our [cookie policy](http://www.wheresbest.co.uk/cookie-policy.php).

When you visit this website, you may view advertisements posted on the site by Google or other companies. These advertising companies may collect information about you while you are visiting this website and other websites. They may use this data to show you advertisements on this website and elsewhere on the Internet about products and services you might like. This website does not collect the information or control the content of the advertisements that you will see. You may be able to opt out of such advertising. To find out more about Google and its DoubleClick DART cookie used to generate interest-based advertising, [click this link](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Wheresbest.co.uk contains links to sites. Wheresbest.co.uk is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site, a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on Wheresbest.co.uk.

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, Wheresbest will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by Wheresbest.co.uk, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the Wheresbest.co.uk Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. Wheresbest reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of Wheresbest or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest.

From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy. If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted. If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.

To change any of the details we hold about you please e-mail us, or use the relevant area of the website.
